<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<product>
  <title>Unification</title>
  <release-dates>
    <release-date>October 2022</release-date>
  </release-dates>
  
  <website>https://crushpoint.games/unification/</website>

  <!-- Link to request press copy: -->
  <press-copy-request>https://dodistribute.com/access/oAoGOmQRfY/</press-copy-request>

  <platforms>
    <platform>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1177340/Unification/</link>
    </platform>
    <platform>
      <name>Oculus App Lab</name>
      <link>https://www.oculus.com/experiences/quest/4244393598953009/</link>
    </platform>
  </platforms>

  <prices>
    <price>
      <currency>USD</currency>
      <value>14.99</value>
    </price>
  </prices>

  <description>
  Unification is a VR roguelike in destructible procedural voxel caves filled with traps and enemies. Use impactful tools to move in unique ways and defeat obstacles. Enjoy fluid physics-based movement with leaping, climbing, and gravity realignment.</description>

  <!-- Or multiple blocks: -->
  
  <histories>
    <history>
      <header>Zero G Debris Climbing</header>
      <text>Latching on floating debris and maintaining momentum</text>
    </history>
    <history>
      <header>Spelunky VR</header>
      <text>Climbing in procedural voxel caves with traps, enemies, and rewards</text>
    </history>
    <history>
      <header>Roguevania</header>
      <text>Branching paths, teleporters, unique biomes, side quests</text>
    </history>
    <history>
      <header>Early Access</header>
      <text>Community feedback driven development</text>
    </history>
  </histories>
  

  <features>
    <feature>
    Fluid and powerful physics-based movement: Feel momentum and the wind rushing past while leaping into chasms, vaulting over ledges, weaving around traps, and realigning gravity at will.
    </feature>
    <feature>
    Impactful and unique tools and weapons: Swing above traps with a grappling hook, or glide past with a parachute. Go in guns blazing with a shotgun, or slice with a katana. Forge a new path with a jackhammer, or warp through with a teleporter.
    </feature>
    <feature>
    Procedural destructible biomes filled with traps and enemies: Navigate through unique voxel cave obstacle courses with branching paths that test your reactions, knowledge, and control. Feel free to explore the depths and get lost. The handheld mini-map and conveniently placed teleporters make it easy to quickly get back on track.
    </feature>
    <feature>
    Carefully crafted controls and haptics: Each action is positioned on the controllers to allow effortless simultaneous usage of all movement and tool capabilities, inducing a flow state of control. Player collisions, damage, climbing, tool usage, and more are fed into haptics for a complete loop of sensory I/O.
    </feature>
  </features>

  <trailers>
    <trailer>
      <name>Unification Trailer</name>

      <!-- Pick one: -->
      <youtube>
        <!-- Video ID only, not the full URL -->
        fAkY-rKQBsI
      </youtube>
    </trailer>
  </trailers>

  <!-- You can set your widgets here (optional): -->
  <widgets>
    <steam>
      <!-- Steam ID -->
      <!-- e.g. 424242 -->
      1177340
    </steam>
  </widgets>

    <!--
  <awards>
    <award>
      <description></description>
      <info></info>
    </award>
  </awards>


  <quotes>
    <quote>
      <description></description>
      <name></name>
      <website></website>
      <link></link>
    </quote>
  </quotes>

  <additionals>
    <additional>
      <title></title>
      <description></description>
      <link></link>
    </additional>
  </additionals>
    -->

  <credits>
    <credit>
      <person>Troy Spencer</person>
      <role>Lead Designer and Lead Programmer</role>

      <!-- Optional: -->
      <website></website>
    </credit>
  </credits>

  <contacts>
    <contact>
      <name>Troy Spencer</name>

      <!-- Pick one: -->
      <link>https://twitter.com/__ZURG__</link>
    </contact>
  </contacts>
</product>
